[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is a common myth concerning the damages caused by a tornado to a house?", "correct_answer": "Opening the windows will lessen the damages.", "incorrect_answers": ["Having trees and shrubs around the house will lessen the damages.", "Tornadoes spare houses painted in orange.", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Some animals have an inborn instinct to swallow gastroliths in order to improve the breaking down of food inside their stomachs. What kind of objects are gastroliths?", "correct_answer": "Rocks", "incorrect_answers": ["Plants that are rich in digestive enzymes", "Insects", "Excrements"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who directed and starred in the 1993 drama movie The Man Without a Face?", "correct_answer": "Mel Gibson", "incorrect_answers": ["Tom Hanks", "John Travolta", "Nicolas Cage"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "6 am:  My alarm went off and my 4-year-old daughter jumped in bed with me, triggering my pedophobia. What was I afraid of?", "correct_answer": "Children", "incorrect_answers": ["Loud noises", "Quick movements", "Daylight"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Does Christopher Walker play Count Dooku in episodes 2 and 3 of Star Wars?", "correct_answer": "No", "incorrect_answers": ["Yes"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1836, German-Dutch farmers in South Africa moved north east through South Africa to establish a colony.  What did they call this march?", "correct_answer": "The Great Trek", "incorrect_answers": ["The March of the 14,000", "The Dutch-Zulu War", "The Boer War"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress received the Academy Award for Best Actress for 1989?", "correct_answer": "Jessica Tandy for Driving Miss Daisy", "incorrect_answers": ["Michelle Pfeiffer for The Fabulous Baker Boys", "Isabelle Adjani for Camille Claudel", "Jessica Lange for Music Box"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The words No thing more excellent nor more valuable than wine was ever granted mankind by God belong to this Greek philosopher.", "correct_answer": "Plato", "incorrect_answers": ["Heraclitus", "Homer", "Socrates"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the 1977 movie Smokie and the Bandit, Burt Reynolds drove a black Ford Taurus.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "There is a unit called a Yottagram. How many grams are in one Yottagram?", "correct_answer": "10^24", "incorrect_answers": ["10^12", "10^18", "10"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which word goes with the Oriental symbol Yang?", "correct_answer": "Yin", "incorrect_answers": ["Tao", "Sutra", "Ying"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What s another name for the chaga mushroom, a parasitic fungus growing mainly on birch trees?", "correct_answer": "Cinder conk", "incorrect_answers": ["All of these", "Ashy mushroom", "Black sparrow"]}]